{
    "subject": "Carlos_Atanes",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "PROXIMA",
    "human_readable": "Carlos Atanes directed PROXIMA.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8874195218086243,
            "question": "Is Carlos Atanes a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8484697341918945,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Carlos Atanes."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.751052737236023,
            "question": "Who directed the film PROXIMA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7482732534408569,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Carlos Atanes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5777345895767212,
            "question": "Can you give an example of another film directed by Carlos Atanes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3538787364959717,
            "question": "What could we learn about Carlos Atanes from this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3204993009567261,
            "question": "What year was PROXIMA released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27050089836120605,
            "question": "Where could we find more information about PROXIMA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2583644390106201,
            "question": "Do you know any actors who appeared in PROXIMA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24450765550136566,
            "question": "What type of media is PROXIMA?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carlos Atanes directed PROXIMA.",
            "html": "yago_8928_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any actors who appeared in PROXIMA?",
            "html": "yago_8928_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where could we find more information about PROXIMA?",
            "html": "yago_8928_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was PROXIMA released?",
            "html": "yago_8928_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8928_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Carlos Atanes and his film Proxima, including that he was the director. Therefore, the statement \"Carlos Atanes directed PROXIMA\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}